Igbadume OmoBruno

🗣 Auchi, Edo, Nigeria 🗷 brownmagnate1@gmail.com 🛘 (+234)9068396734 📠 https://www.linkedin.com/in/brown-magnate-b1213b1b6/

■ brownmagnate.tk

SUMMARY

a creative civil engineer with a passion for design. I have been working as a graphic designer for the past four years and absolutely love bringing ideas to life through visual communication Whether it's branding for a new business, creating social media graphics, or designing packaging for a product, I am up for the challenge and ready to bring my unique perspective to the table. I am a problem-solver at heart and love using both my creative and technical skills to tackle new challenges.

EXPERIENCE

Brand Identity Designer and Social Media Manager

May 2022 - Present, Nigeria

- Slay's Exchange
- · Designed brand identity for the company
- · Created unique visual language for the brand
- · Developed overall look and feel for the company

Brand Designer

Ace Tech

January 2022 - Present, Nigeria

- · Crafted a unified visual brand design vision, leveraging Adobe Creative Suite, resulting in a 10% increase in customer engagement and an 8% increase in online sales.
- · Developed recognizable and effective style guide that established new visual language, meeting design standards and ensured consistency in messaging across all mediums.
- · Produced graphic content such as logos, icons, illustrations, advertisements, web banners, and print products.

Brand Designer and Social Media Manager

Nuel's Exchange

January 2022 - Present, Nigeria

- · Created engaging content for digital campaigns and accounts across various social media platforms, resulting in an average engagement rate of 25% and a reach of an average of 500 thousand unique users.
- · Developed the visual identity for several product launches, resulting in a 37% increase in conversions and a 57% lift in brand related
- · Implemented innovative strategies to create brand-focused web assets, increasing organic traffic by 25%.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Science in Engineering

Ambrose Alli Unversity Ekpoma · Nigeria · 2022

SKILLS

Graphic Design, Motion Graphics, Animation Art